planning out the customer experience and sales path on each page.
We didn't touch on the latest trends in lead generations like quizzes and assessments and mini membership sites. We didn't talk about artificial intelligence or chatbots or NFTs, blockchain ownerships, virtual reality.
But thankfully, Terry Brock is gonna cover those elements and more. So don't don't miss his session.
There's just a lot going on with Web3, and websites are changing fast and trying to keep up.
I hope we sparked something for you, an idea of how you might improve your most valuable online asset, your website.
And because we covered so much so fast, we've built an online audit for you. Now, this audit will walk you through some of the key elements that we've talked about here and a little bit more.
We'll talk about design, functionality, accessibility, and customer experience.
And you can take the time and think about whether that makes sense for your business and figure out what changes you may need to make now to implement to get your site next-gen ready.
There's a link to the audit in your handout, and I urge you to make the time to take it.
It'll probably take you 3 minutes.
Thank you so much, and I hope I get to see you in person in Calgary in December.
So here's a virtual one for now, and there's a real one coming.
Thanks, everybody. Bye.
Awesome. All right. I know our, our Lorne is here online with us. Lorne, are you able to join us?
I'm here.
All right, let me find you here. I gotta find you to spotlight. Anthony, if you see— let's see, or let me see, where is—
there she is.
Yes. All right, everybody, so, so first of all, let me say, um, I'm so glad that you're here, but I'm so sad that you're here because that means you're not on vacation, that you have been—
I'm not in Blue Ridge for a long, long, long time.
So hopefully you do get to fly out tomorrow.
Thank you. If there are questions live and in person for Lauren, she is more than willing to answer them. So throw them into the chat.
Anything that you have.
First of all, I want to add my two cents in here. I love that whole AI feature.
I had no idea looking at that and seeing how that can improve my site. So thank you. Thank you for that big tip.
Other things that you want to find information.
Let's see if there's any questions.
Uh, let's see.
Please put them in the chat, put a question in front of them so we can find them if they're there.
Carol has her hand up. Oh, awesome. Carol, go ahead.
I had my hand up like a few times before and nobody ever saw it, I guess because it's like yellow behind me.
So it was like camouflage.
Um, I think actually Sarah already answered it in the chat. I wanted to know whether or not the— like how to get that widget because I think it's phenomenal.
Um, but apparently it's code.
So I can just talk to you when you're updating my website.
Yeah, yeah, I mean, and there's, there's, there are plugins that you can get, WordPress plugins for accessibility, but they don't always work.
So yeah, if you want to, you can, you can take the audit, and there's a link to chat with us after you take it.
So if you have questions like that, please feel free to go ahead and do that.
Cool.
Thank you.
Patricia had a question. Patricia, do you wanna come online and ask it?
Sure. When I first heard your tip in the preview video, I went looking and I grab a lot of my, my photos from Canva.
They have a brand new option that I didn't see not too long ago.
SVG, best for web design and animations. Is that the kind of sizing that you're talking about?
Gonna let Sarah throw that in the chat just because I don't want to be wrong.
Well, that's why I have a team, right?
Because sure, there's, there's, yeah, things that I don't know.
Okay, you know what?